Finding aid for the June L. Mazer Lesbian Archives Collection of Video Materials, 1980-2005 LSC.2231
UCLA Library Special Collections
June L. Mazer Lesbian Archives Collection of Video Materials
1980-2005
UCLA Library Special Collections
June L. Mazer Lesbian Archives
LSC.2231
4 linear feet (4 record cartons)
This collection of videos includes commercial and home made productions that touch on issues of feminism, lesbians, and relevant LGBT topics. Videos were culled from the personal collections of individuals such as Diane Germain, Ester Bentley, and Angela Brinskele.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
COLLECTION CONTAINS AUDIOVISUAL MATERIALS: Collection is currently being digitized. Special equipment or further processing may be required for viewing. If you have questions about this material please email spec-coll@library.ucla.edu.
Acquisition Information
Provenance unknown.
This collection is part of an outreach and collection-building partnership between the June L. Mazer Lesbian Archives, the UCLA Center for the Study of Women (CSW), and the UCLA Library.
Historical Note
This collection of videos includes commercial and home made productions that touch on issues of feminism, lesbians, and broader LGBT related topics.
Scope and Content
Videos were culled from the personal collections of individuals such as Diane Germain, Ester Bentley, and Angela Brinskele.
Organization and Arrangement
Materials are arranged according to original provenance or collection from which they were culled.
Location Note
Ester F. Bentley papers (Collection 1981). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles.
Diane Germain papers (Collection 1961). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles.
Angela Brinskele photographs (Collection 2158). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles.
Old Lesbians Organizing for Change records (Collection 2203). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles.
Southern California Women for Understanding (SCWU) collection (Collection 2203). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, University of California, Los Angeles.
- Ester Bentley Collection, 1983-1987; Series 1.
  - Papal Visit (John Paul II) to L.A.; The motorcade - Prayer Service at the Cathedral of Saint Vibiana - Meeting with youth at Universal Amphitheatre [Gibson Ampitheatre] - Address to Communication Industry, 15 September 1987 (Box 1, Item 1)
  - Tape 2 of "Papal Visit (John Paul II) to L.A.": 9/15 Mass at the Coliseum; 9/16 Special on the Vatican, 15-16 September 1987 (Box 1, Item 2)
  - [TAPE 3] 9/16: End of visit to Immaculate Conception School; meeting at Japanese Cultural Center [JACCC], World Religion Leaders; only part of pre-Mass at Dodger Stadium; Mass at Dodger Stadium; last part of tape is the pre-Mass program (almost all of it)., 16 September 1983 (Box 1, Item 3)
- Califia, 1983; Series 2.
  - Califia #1 of 8. 8-14,15, 83; DFG [Diane F. Germain]. M. [Marilyn] Murphy. Sexism. C. [Cathy] White, Video Verte., 14-15 August 1983 (Box 1, Item 4)
    Scope and Contents note
    [From the included handwritten index]: 8 Califia Community Tapes 1983 Previously owned by Califia Community Documented on tape by collective Tape #1 0000 M.M. [Marilyn Murphy] Intro to Califia - history 0530 Collective introduced 0744 D.F.G. [Diane F. Germain] photography 1659 Begin terms (tape terms) 1750 D.F.G. Talks video 1850 Cathy talks terms 1950 D.F.G. two tapes to be made 2185 daughter circle piece 2315 Dr. Betty Brooks Workshop on Sexism (Jetta) 3273 D.F.G. Fortune and men's eyes 3333 Muriel Fisher and D.F.G. story of 4th of July fight 3480 Rockey talks about 50's Dykes (short) 3909 D.F.G. intuition piece 4209 D.F.G. and G.A. [Gretchen Alspach] hair freedom piece 4360 Muriel and Web 4440 D.F.G. pornog. workshop *tape ideas 5011 grey area 5050 Community meeting 5100 Weaving web problem 5141 D.F.G. web defense 5280 D.F.G. web talk Food. Discussion also. 5859 Stop end of tape Cathy White - photographer
  - Califia Community - Racism seminar - Tape 2 of 8. CWhite Video Verte., 15-16 August 1983 (Box 1, Item 5)
  - Califia Community - Classism seminar - Tape 3 of 8. Committee Meeting/Auction. WO Image Slideshow. CWhite Video Verte., 17 August 1983 (Box 1, Item 6)
  - Califia Community - Abled-Disabled Workshop, Sock Hop - Tape 4 of 8. Auction, SWOC. CWhite Video Verte., 17-18 August 1983 (Box 1, Item 7)
  - Califia Community - Talent Show - Tape 5 of 8. Kitchen, Talent Show. CWhite., 19 August 1983 (Box 1, Item 8)
  - Califia Community - Collective Meeting, Kitchen Samba - Tape 6 of 8. CWhite., 20 August 1983 (Box 1, Item 9)
  - Califia Community - Procession, Banquet, Women of Color. #7 of 8. CWhite., 20 August 1983 (Box 1, Item 10)
  - Califia Community - Closing, circle gypsy - Tape 8 of 8 C.White, 21 August 1983 (Box 1, Item 11)
- Diane Germain, 1986-2004; Series 3.
  - [A Lesbian Decade: The San Diego Seventies, Tape #1] Interview with Bonnie Zimmerman and Sue Palmer., 1991 (Box 4, Item 1)
  - [A Lesbian Decade: The San Diego Seventies, Tape #2] Interview with Bridget Wilson and Kim McAlister., 1991 (Box 4, Item 2)
  - [A Lesbian Decade: The San Diego Seventies, Tape #3] Interview with Bridget Wilson and Kim McAlister., 1991 (Box 4, Item 3)
  - [A Lesbian Decade: The San Diego Seventies, Tape #4] Group interview: Diane F. Germain and Pam Wilson; Karen Merry and Cory Baca; River Malcom; Kathy Moore and Deanne Gauthier., 1991 (Box 4, Item 4)
  - [A Lesbian Decade: The San Diego Seventies, Tape #5] Interview: "Las Hermanas" (Marinel Weaver, Roberta Gonzales-Gregg, Teresa Oyos, and Virginia Martins); Johnola Hughes; "Paige" Brown., 1991 (Box 4, Item 5)
  - [A Lesbian Decade: The San Diego Seventies, Tape #6] Interview: "Las Hermanas" (Marinel Weaver, Roberta Gonzales-Gregg, Teresa Oyos, and Virginia Martins); Johnola Hughes; "Paige" Brown., 1991 (Box 4, Item 6)
  - [A Lesbian Decade: The San Diego Seventies, Tape #7] Interview with Pat Cluchey and Paradigm Book Store., 1991 (Box 4, Item 7)
  - [A Lesbian Decade: The San Diego Seventies, Tape #8] Interview with "Paige" Brown., 1991 (Box 4, Item 8)
  - [A Lesbian Decade: The San Diego Seventies, Tape #9] Interview with Bonnie Zimmerman and Sue Palmer., 1991 (Box 4, Item 9)
  - [A Lesbian Decade: The San Diego Seventies, Tape #10] Interview with Diane F. Germain and Pam Wilson; Cory Baca and Karen Merry; Deanne Gauthier and Kathy Moore., 1991 (Box 4, Item 10)
  - [A Lesbian Decade: The San Diego Seventies, Tape #11] Interview with Cynthia Laurence-Wallace and Peggy Heathers., 1991 (Box 4, Item 11)
  - [A Lesbian Decade: The San Diego Seventies, Tape #12] Interview with Cynthia Laurence-Wallace and Peggy Heathers., 1991 (Box 4, Item 12)
  - [A Lesbian Decade: The San Diego Seventies, Tape #13] Interview with Edna Myers., 1991 (Box 4, Item 13)
  - [A Lesbian Decade: The San Diego Seventies, Tape #14] Overview., 1991 (Box 4, Item 14)
  - [Herstorical Snippets: Diane and Teacher Protest, 5-28-2004] San Diego teachers rally against health care benefits cuts.--Recording of Manny & Lo. (Box 4, Item 15)
  - [Herstorical Snippets: Ellen Show news reports] San Diego local news reports on lesbian and gay people watching the "herstorical" Ellen Show when she "came out," including Diane Germain, Pamela Gusha, and Gayle Feldman., 1997 (Box 4, Item 16)
  - [Herstorical Snippets: Hate Flyers] Diane Germain speaks about racist flyers posted in Hillcrest. Also contains partial recording of the movie "China Girl.", 1992 (Box 4, Item 17)
  - [Herstorical Snippets: Mental Health, Asian Women] Cross Cultural Issues workshop #2, seminar on refugees. Diane Germain (UCSD Medical Center, social worker) asks questions about why women don't receive mental health care., 1990 (Box 4, Item 18)
  - [Herstorical Snippets: Myth California Arrest] Germain is arrested protesting the "Myth California Pageant" for littering corn flakes, 1987 (Box 4, Item 19)
    Ann Simonton (Santa Cruz) in corn flakes box is also arrested. In total, 11 women and 1 man are arrested.--Catherine Johns (San Diego) has a panel discussion on beauty pageants. Germain (Califia Community Collective) and Abbie Padgett (NOW, ACLU) speak about the objectification of women for profit.--Report on settlement that three women receive a year later after being arrested unjustly.
  - [Herstorical Snippets: Ann Simonton "Myth California"] Fred Lewis interviews with Ann Simonton (Director of Myth California protests, former bathing suit model for Sports Illustrated).--Germain arrested--Germain and Padgett discuss the pageant., 1986-1987 (Box 4, Item 20)
  - [Herstorical Snippets: Lesbian Cartoonist] Linda Gibbins of "Our World" Television interviews Diane F. Germain, lesbian cartoonist., January 1993 (Box 4, Item 21)
  - Tape content descriptions, 1980s (Box 4)
  - 2 Unlabeled Super 8 tapes, undated (Box 4)
- Curation Series: Angela Brinskele, Series 4.
  - Mazer Festival - Room of Our Own #1 of 3, 10/16/1994 (Box 2, Item 1)
  - [Italian American Women's Reading at Mama Bear's, Oakland], April 1997 (Box 2, Item 2)
    From box: Produced by Francesca Roccaforte, Camera by Debra Arbuckle, Gable. With Giovanna (Janet) Capone, Lucia Chiavola Birnbaum, Sabina Magilocco, Corva Rose Radici.
  - [Dykes and Their Dogs] Starring Carleasei (MC), Clancey (Trickster), Ester Bently (Prizemaker),and The Dogbreath Band. Produced and written by Mary jo Godgess and Renee Sotile; World Premiere at Los Angeles' Outfest 2000. (Box 2, Item 3)
    From box: "An uproarious musical/comedy Dykeumentary about the popular Dykes and Their Dogs contest held annually in West Hollywood, California. This is not just another day in the park. With contest categories showcasing: Most Butch, Most Femme, Best Singer, Best Kisser and Best Owner-Look-Alike, it is hard to distinguish who is really performing the tricks, the Dykes or the Dogs. Filled with a rainbow of characters, some four-legged, some two-legged, and some "somewhere in between." Unconditional love sets a resounding tone. The original soundtrack literally Pants & Howls with the title track anthem, "I'm a Dyke, I'm a Dog!!! A veritable sing-a-long whether you are a Dyke, or a Dog, or "somewhere in between.""
  - [Bessie, Billie, & Ruth] "Divas Breaking Taboos," starring Renee Sotile and Mary Jo Godges., 2003 (Box 2, Item 4)
  - [Lipstick Lesbians], undated (Box 2, Item 5)
  - [Lesbian Images] A class by Lauren Jardine: pictures various interviews with lesbians and lesbian couples talking about their own experience as lesbians (in their youth and at present). Video by Linmar Productions., 1990; VHS (Box 2, Item 6)
    [Lesbian Images] A class by Lauren Jardine: pictures various interviews with lesbians and lesbian couples talking about their own experience as lesbians (in their youth and at present). Video by Linmar Productions.
  - [Que Sera] A collection of footage and memorabilia from Que Sera (once a popular Long Beach bar for lesbians), 1975-1995. Features a performance by the Que Serettes. (Box 2, Item 7)
  - [Texas Bullsh!t] By Renee Sotile and Mary Jo Godges., 2004 (Box 2, Item 8)
  - [Greetings from Washington D.C.] March on Washington, 1979. (Box 2, Item 9)
  - [Presentation of Plaques, June Mazer] (Box 2, Item 10)
  - [Hearts & Hands; A Stitch in Time; Remember My Name; The Way We Wear] (Box 2, Item 11)
  - [Miscellaneous Queer TV Coverage] Recording includes: Propaganda Film, Cammemeyer testimony, Achtenberg debate, gay and lesbian issues, accuracy in the media., 1993 (Box 2, Item 12)
  - [Lesbian and Gay Youth Video Project--British Youth], 1982 (Box 2, Item 13)
  - [Oprah interviews], 1987, 1989 (Box 2, Item 14)
    Episode recordings of Oprah: interview with lesbian women (1987, includes Yolanda Ritter on panel) and a special on "Coming Out" in honor of National Coming Out Day (1989). Transfer also contains the movie "Entre nous" (1983).
  - [Geraldo episodes] (Box 2, Item 15)
    Includes Geraldo/Cheryl Crane interview, "Gays in Uniform" Geraldo episode (May 1988), and "Lesbian and Gay Rights" (1987)
  - [Miscellaneous TV Coverage of Lesbian/Gay Issues, California] (Box 2, Item 16)
    From tape: Lesbian/gay marriages, Larry King reparative therapy, Brain Study LeVey, In the Shadow of Love, Teen Aids, Cher Bio, Dear John Episode, Stop the Church, Protests AB101 (A. Donnahoe, C.Fisher, Lily Tomlin), Discussion on Aids Ten Years Later.
  - [In My Own Words] The story of the first African-American woman to gain entrace into the INternational Brotherhood of Electrical Workers., 1992 (Box 2, Item 17)
    Also labeled as "Against All Odds: Women in the Trades." Attributed to Neshtey Crudup, Lynn Dabney, and Vivian Price.
  - [West Hollywood City Channel 10] Labeled "1.9" and Show #3.", October 1997 (Box 2, Item 18)
  - [Tiny & Ruby: Hell Divin' Wimmon], 1989 (Box 2, Item 19)
    Pictures legendary jazz trumpeter Tiny Davis and her partner of over 40 years, drummer-pianist Ruby Lucas. Produced and directed by Greta Schiller and Andrea Weiss.
  - [Long Beach Lesbian and Gay Pride] Long Beach parade with Mazer board member Cheryl Nassar., May 17, 1992 (Box 2, Item 20)
  - [Various TV News Clips] Miscellaneous television recordings on lesbian/gay marriage, brain studies, domestic partners, Cher, AIDS, AB101 and protests., circa 1980's-1990's (Box 2, Item 21)
  - Archives Building Fund - A Short Videotape. LHEF (Lesbian Herstory Educational Foundation)., circa 1980s (Box 2, Item 22)
  - Mazer Festival- A Room of Our Own, 16 October 1994 (Box 2, Item 23)
  - Mazer Festival - Room of Our Own #2 of 3, 10/16/1994 (Box 2, Item 24)
  - Mazer & Cool Sponsored Panel Discussion at Plummer Park, West Hollywood, 07/22/1995 (Box 2, Item 25)
  - Middlesex: Redefining He She (Box 2, Item 26)
  - Ret Coller Memorial, 06/10/1994 (Box 2, Item 27)
  - A Celebration of the Life of Audre Lorde, 02/27/1994; VHS (Box 2, Item 28)
    A Celebration of the Life of Audre Lorde
  - OLOC Banquet (Box 2, Item 29)
  - West Coast Celebration Sunday OLOC, 1987 April (Box 2, Item 30)
  - Vera Martin's 75th Birthday. Video by Cristina Vegas, 06/20/1998 (Box 2, Item 31)
  - In the Life, 2003 (Box 2, Item 32)
  - Rachel Rosenthal Life & Times, 02/10/1994 (Box 2, Item 33)
  - The Sisterhood Bookstore 25th Anniversary Celebration, with Gloria Steinem, Bell Hooks, Sheila Kuehl, Maxine Waters, Emily Levine, Eloise Klein Healy, Jackie Goldberg, and Robin Tyler., 11/23/1997 (Box 2, Item 34)
  - [Tret Fure; Chris Williamson; 1st Part of Gloria Allred], [c.a. 1984] (Box 2, Item 35)
    Musical performances, brief speeches/commentary, comedic acts. Topics ranging from being drug free, discussion of the imprisonment of women, classism, social justice, and creating women-only safe spaces.
  - Diane's Humor at SOL - Diane Makes Jokes, 04/14/1991 (Box 2, Item 36)
  - Lesbian Health Heros Thanks Diane! by Cindy Nelson, 1993 (Box 2, Item 37)
  - BLT Lesbian Delights, October 1988 (Box 2, Item 38)
  - G. Steinam, undated (Box 2, Item 39)
  - [Get Used To It - "Education"] Episode #20 of the TV program Get Used To It, focused on education., 1994 (Box 3, Item 1)
    Hosted by Sheila James Kuehl; guests Jeff Horton and Bonnie Castrey. Contains interview with Jackie Goldberg, lesbian member of the Los Angeles City Council and former member of the Los Angeles Unified School District Board. Discussion of LGBT youth/students, allies, administrators, teachers, etc. Topics include tolerance, sexual education, dress codes, prom, and multicultural integration. Aired 11/15/1994, filmed at 8611 Santa Monica Blvd, West Hollywood, California.
  - [Pride Divide] By Paris Poirier and Karen Kiss., 1997 (Box 3, Item 2)
    A multicity work focusing on men and women in LGBT history. Topics include community formation and rivalry, police persecution, HIV/AIDS, legal issues, myths and stereotypes, and contesting opinions. Includes a vast group of speakers: Joan Nestle, Nadine Smith, Eric Gutirrez, Kate Clinton, Joanne Lulan, Camille Paglia, Eric Morris, Harry Hay, Rose Trouche, Michael Musto, Jim Kepner, Sarah Pettit, Torie Osborn, Phyllis Lyon, Del Martin, Barbara Gittings, and Lillian Faderman.
  - [Richard's Things], 1980 (Box 3, Item 3)
    From the tape: "Gloomy drama about a widow who gets seduced by her late husband's girlfriend." Starring Liv Ulmann, Amanda Redman, and David Markham. Based on Frederic Raphael's novel of the same name. Directed by Anthony Harvey.
  - [Women Are Not Cartoons], 1991 (Box 3, Item 4)
    Play with small cast comprised of various roles and vignettes. Topics include honesty in relationships, sexual openness, friendship, flirtation, etc. Repeated use of fade to black with audio overlay - not a technical glitch.
  - [Dykes on Mikes], 1991 (Box 3, Item 5)
    Musical performances and brief commentary. Note on VHS label puts runtime at 1 hour 55 minutes, but video and audio cut out completely after 48 minutes of play. Intermittent picture interruption and glitches.
  - [No On 64 - Stop LaRouche], 1986 (Box 3, Item 6)
    Actress Patty Duke pleads with Californians to vote no on Proposition 64, the initiative to restore AIDS to the list of communicable diseases.
  - [The Woman's Building: Women's Video Access Workshop Summer 1987 - "Successful Women: Options, Choices, Solutions"] (Box 3, Item 7)
    Overview of various women-oriented services in Los Angeles, such as THE (To Help Everyone) Clinic, Alcoholism Center for Women, Chicana Service Action Center, Connexus, and the Girls Club of Santa Monica/Bay Area.
  - [Shasta Woman - The Story of Norma Jean Croy], c.a. 1993 (Box 3, Item 8)
    Video detailing case information of Norma Jean Croy, a Native American woman wrongfully sentenced to life in prison for first degree murder in 1978. Diane Samuelson, a defense team attorney, narrates frequently. Interviews with Norma Jean Croy, Johnell Sanchez, Nilak Butler, and Yvonne Swan Sinixt. Discussion of Native American life in California, racial profiling, the legal/justice system, and life in prison.
  - [Lesbian Physicians on Practice, Patients, & Power], 1991 (Box 3, Item 9)
    Interviews with medical students and medical professionals. Topics include coming out to patients, issues in medical education, the work/home divide, and other unique challenges faced by lesbians in the medical field.
  - ["World of Light: A Portrait of May Sarton"] (Box 3, Item 10)
    Extended talk with poet/author May Sarton about her work and life. Themes include endurance, fan letters, her relationship with her mother, metaphor, women's literature, and the legacy of her writing. Includes footage of Sarton walking through the woods, visiting the post office, smoking, talking with others, gardening, reading her work, etc.
  - [Concert Highlights of Olivia Records 15th Anniversary], c.a. 1990 (Box 3, Item 11)
    Anniversary concert for Olivia Records, a collective for women's music. Includes brief interviews and commentary. Participants include Deidre McCalla, Dianne Davidson, Tret Fure, Lucie Blue Tremblay, and Cris Williamson. Produced by Kathy Wolfe and Judy Dlugacz. Video is often poor and image cuts out intermittently.
  - [Gloria Allred; Margaret Gomez; Mother Tongue Reader's Theater; Workshops; Lynn Lavner], c.a. 1985 (Box 3, Item 12)
    Gloria Allred speaking about the 1983 Papa Choux discrimination case, and talking with audience members afterward. Various acts including comedian Margaret Gomez and the Mother Tongue Reader's Theater. Video cuts off abruptly and switches to numerous workshops at a camp rally in Georgia. Topics in the workshops include the family unit, political activism, nuclear proliferation, discrimination, and feminism. Video cuts to performance of lesbian comedian/performer Lynn Lavner.
  - [Tour of the Mazer Collection] Interviews with volunteers including Jo Duffy, Irene Walt, and Lauren Hines., c.a. 1990 (Box 3, Item 13)
    Content includes background on June L. Mazer, community involvement in the collection, and an overview of holdings including posters, buttons, publications, pulp novels, fiction books, ephemera, and the video collection.
  - [Flo Kennedy; Cassie Culver; Brown Bag Theater], c.a. 1983 (Box 3, Item 14)
    Flo Kennedy discussing letters, the intersection of love and sex, fundraising, personal empowerment, the presidential election of 1984 (particularly the Mondale-Ferraro ticket), Vanessa Williams' Miss America scandal, and interacting with the audience. Lesbian feminist singer Cassie Culver performs various songs and explains the political/social messages behind them. The Brown Bag Theater group performs on the topics of identity and womanhood in relation to alcoholism.
  - [Claudia's Birthday Party] Informal footage of a birthday party., 1989 (Box 3, Item 15)
  - [Califia Talent Show], 1985 (Box 3, Item 16)
    Highlights of the 1985 Califia (women's community) talent show. Begins with an overview of the camp and various activities, including crafts, family time, and remembrances. Performers include Kate Rosenblatt (guitar), Alice Eldred (yodeling), along with dramatic readings, poetry, and various musical and comedy sketches.
  - [Closets Are Health Hazards: Lesbian and Gay Physicians Come Out], 1986 (Box 3, Item 17)
  - [Lavender Underground #2; Chumash Pow Wow], 1993 (Box 3, Item 18)
    Footage from Lavender Underground #2, Valentine's Day Weekend, February of 1993. MC Jean Wiley, with performances by Cindy Kallet and others. / Footage from the Chumash (Native American) Pow Wow in Baldwin Park, California, c.a. 1990.
  - [TV Clips - After Stonewall; NBC News; Cheryl Crane; Lynn Scher/Katherine Lee Bates] (Box 3, Item 19)
    After Stonewall (airdate August 18, 2000) on Los Angeles KCET. Special examining the social and political aftermath of the Stonewall Riots in 1969. NBC News - August 23, 2000. Coverage of a lesbian couple who was asked to leave Dodger Stadium after complaints about them kissing, and the Stadium's subsequent apology. Cheryl Crane interview on Larry King Live August 8, 2001. CSPAN Book TV from December 16, 2001 with Lynn Scher (America the Beautiful) and Katherine Lee Bates.
  - [Gay Cable TV] Various clips from GCN, the Gay Cable Network. (Box 3, Item 20)
    Includes news coverage and interviews concerning multiple gay pride events and AIDS awareness events. In-depth coverage of Gay Pride Day at King's Island Amusement Park. Also, coverage of the national march on Washington about AIDS, gay civil rights, and racism. Features information about the Names Project quilt exhibition in Cincinnati, Ohio; multiple quilts bearing names and designs representative of significant contributors to LGBT history.
  - [Califia Talent Show - Autumn 1984] (Box 3, Item 21)
    Highlights from the Califia (women's community) talent show. Performers are unidentified. Performances include singing, dramatic readings, and comedy. Multiple singing acts are choreographed with sign language.
  - [Olivia Cruise to the Caribbean], 1990 (Box 3, Item 22)
    Highlights of a 1990 Olivia Cruises journey to the Caribbean. Notable clips include dancing, a wedding, brief comedy acts, and a costume party.
  - [Kay Weaver, Gini Clemmen, Joanna Cazden] (Box 3, Item 23)
    Performances at a Women's Camp festival, including camp announcements and comedic MC performances between musical acts. Special recognition given to multiple sign language interpreters for providing access to women with hearing difficulties.
  - [9 Clips] (Box 3, Item 24)